Richard, if your dinners are like this every night,
Richard, 如果你们家的晚饭每天都像今天这么丰盛的话,
I'm going to be a very jealous man.
那我要嫉妒死你了.
Oh, absolutely. Five courses. Candlelight.
Oh, 当然啦. 有五道大菜. 还有烛光呢.
It is so easy to please Richard.
Richard这个人很容易满足.
Sorry guys. I've been here.
不好意思, 伙计们. 我可是来过这里.
I've seen the Chinese food cartons.
看到的可是中式快餐饭盒.
I told you he was easy to please.
我告诉过你们他这个人很容易满足.
Any food will make Richard happy.
Richard不管吃什么都很满意.
You're lucky, Nancy.
你可真幸运, Nancy.
I cook,
我每天都做饭,
and half the time he's too tired to eat.
可是有一半的时候他都累得吃不下去.
We eat too late.
我们吃得太晚了.
You don't get home until 8 o'clock.
问题是你常常要到8点钟以后才能到家呀.
So you guys have been putting in a lot of hours?
这么说你们大家的工作时间都很长吗?
Who isn't?
谁不是这样呢?
Really. Well, I bought a lottery ticket.
说的是啊. Well, 我买了一张彩票.
Uh-oh. What happened to my practical partner?
Uh-oh. 我那讲究实际的搭档是怎么了?
What do you all want when I win?
要是我中奖了你们大家想要什么?
Douglas, honey, you and I are taking a cruise.
Douglas, 亲爱的, 我们俩去航海吧.
Is it too much to ask for a new sailboat?
我想要艘新的帆船不过分吧?
You got it, Joe.
没问题, Joe.
I'll have one, too.
那我也要一艘.
No, no, Richard.
不，不, Richard.
Yvonne should make a big contribution to your campaign.
Yvonne应该捐一大笔钱资助你竞选.
No, no, no, no, hey... We have not yet decided that.
不, 不, 不, 不, 不, hey... 我们还没有决定呢.
What haven't you decided?
你们还没有决定什么?
If Richard is going to run for Attorney General.
Richard是否要竞选首席检察官.
-Oh.   -Ow.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
真对不起. 我还不知道呢.
I guess Joe was too busy to tell me.
我想可能是Joe太忙了, 忘了告诉我.
-Ow.   -I'm sorry dear. Was that your foot?
-Ow.   -对不起, 亲爱的. 是你的脚吗?